<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Recipe | Paul's Personal Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://paultravers.github.io/blog/categories/recipe/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://paultravers.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2017-03-29T13:49:47-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://paultravers.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Paul Travers]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veggie Stir Fry]]></title>
    <link href="http://paultravers.github.io/blog/2017/03/29/veggie-stir-fry/"/>
    <updated>2017-03-29T13:48:24-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://paultravers.github.io/blog/2017/03/29/veggie-stir-fry</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://thepioneerwoman.com/cooking/veggie-stir-fry/">http://thepioneerwoman.com/cooking/veggie-stir-fry/</a></p>

<p>Ingredients:</p>

<p>Heat some oil in a large, heavy skillet over medium-high heat. Add some chunks of onion and chunks of bell pepper. I used red and yellow, but you can use green or even purple if you have them! The veggies you use in this dish are up to you. Just add the firmer veggies first, to give them a chance to cook.</p>

<p>Stir the veggies around the pan for a couple of minutes to let them start cooking. You want them to get some nice color on the outside, so if you need to crank up the heat a little more, feel free!</p>

<p>Then add some minced garlic and cook it for about a minute more, stirring continuously to make sure the garlic doesn’t burn.</p>

<p>Now you can start throwing in the other veggies! Add big chunks of zucchini…</p>

<p>And stir it in, cooking for 2 minutes more.</p>

<p>Next up: Broccoli!</p>

<p>Stir and cook this for a couple of minutes, too.</p>

<p>While the veggies are still somewhat firm, pour in the sauce…</p>

<p>Then stir it and cook it for 1 to 2 minutes more, or until the sauce is very thick. If you feel the veggies need a little more sauciness, stir in &frac14; to &frac12; cup hot water and splash in a little more soy. Easy!</p>

<p>In a small bowl, mix together some soy sauce, sherry, brown sugar, cornstarch, sriracha, and fresh ginger. Yum! Set this aside for a second.
&frac12; cup Low Sodium Soy Sauce
2 Tablespoons Sherry (or Low-sodium Vegetable Broth)
2 Tablespoons Packed Brown Sugar
2 Tablespoons Cornstarch
2 Tablespoons Sriracha (more Or Less To Taste)
1 Tablespoon Minced Fresh Ginger</p>

<p>3 Tablespoons Peanut Oil
1 whole Yellow Onion, Cut Into Large Chunks
1 whole Red Bell Pepper, Seeded And Cut Into Large Chunks
1 whole Yellow Bell Pepper, Seeded And Cut Into Large Chunks
2 whole Garlic Cloves, Minced
2 whole Medium Zucchini, Cut Into Large Wedges
1 head Broccoli Cut Into Florets
Cooked Noodles Or Rice, For Serving</p>

<p>Salad:</p>

<p><a href="http://allrecipes.com/recipe/15177/famous-japanese-restaurant-style-salad-dressing/">http://allrecipes.com/recipe/15177/famous-japanese-restaurant-style-salad-dressing/</a></p>

<p>&frac12; cup minced onion
&frac12; cup peanut oil
1/3 cup rice wine vinegar
2 tablespoons water
2 tablespoons minced fresh ginger root
2 tablespoons minced celery
2 tablespoons ketchup
4 teaspoons soy sauce
2 teaspoons white sugar (brown?)
2 teaspoons lemon juice
&frac12; teaspoon minced garlic
&frac12; teaspoon salt
&frac14; teaspoon ground black pepper</p>

<p>Clean:
<a href="https://youtu.be/KLGSLCaksdY">https://youtu.be/KLGSLCaksdY</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
